

Le Anh Vinh

Solution Architecture

Date of birth: Aug 19, 1982

Gender: Male

Phone: 0905244242

Email: vinhladn@gmail.com

Address: DaNang, Vietnam

OBJECTIVE

Take advantages of software development skills & experiences and understanding of the new techniques and the Agile & Scrum to become a professional Programmer and bring a lot of value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to the development of the company.

EDUCATION

July 2003 - Sep 2006	Aptech Major: Higher Diploma in Sofware Engineering
July 2006 - Nov 2006	Toefl Certificate Da Nang University
March 2017 - Sep 2018	English Communication IRIS Center

WORK EXPERIENCE

July 2019 - Present

FPT SOFTWARE

Solution Architecture

Main responsibilities:

- Planning and tracking the project
- Participate to consult solution for project
- Participate Interview
- Implement the new features and maintenance the system
- Analysis of the requirement
- Design infrastructure with Microservices
- Review code
- Define the conventions for project
- Consultant the solution to customer
- Analyze and implement the project skeleton

Aug 2017 - July 2019

MTI TECHNOLOGY

Project Lead

Main responsibilities:

- Planning and tracking the project
- Participate training for other members
- Participate Interview
- Manage the project
- Analysis of the requirement
- Design infrastructure with Azure Cloud
- Build up the Development & Production server with Azure Cloud

- Set un a	PRODUCTION	environment in	Azura Cloud
- Set up a	PRODUCTION	environnent ir	i Azure Gloud

- Create test cases & Do interaction test

July 2016 - Jun 2017

DAC Tech Company

Senior Java Developer

- Analyst design database
- Research new technology
- Create test cases
- Do interaction test
- Support member fix bugs
- Training

March 2014 - July 2016

Evizi Company

Senior Java Developer

- Maintenace product
- Research new technology
- Create test cases
- Do interaction test
- Support member fix bugs
- Training

March 2013 - March 2014

FPT Software Company

Senior Java Developer & Technical Leader

- Maintenace product
- Research new technology
- Support member fix bugs
- Training

July 2010 - March 2013

QGS Company (From now change to Qup Company)

Java Developer & Team Leader

- Analyst design database
- Programming
- Research new technology
- Fix bugs

July 2006 - March 2010

VTI Corporation

.NET Developer

- Analyst design database
- Programming
- Research new technology
- Fix bugs

ACTIVITIES

April 2016 - April 2016

DEV DAY IN DA NANG

Bach Khoa University

- Attend organize events
- Introduce company to students
- Get the CVs

From 2017 - To 2017

MVP Certicate at DAC Company

CERTIFICATIONS

2021 AZ-304: Microsoft Azure Architect Design

bf032782f1cb/public_url

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/0d2654d9-c564-46a8-b004-

AZ-303: Microsoft Azure Architect Technologies

https://www.credly.com/badges/6f7c602c-b1dd-4f43-b446-

43156864cc55/public_url

Azure Solution Architecture Expert

https://www.credly.com/badges/bfa1591c-6f5f-412c-a77a-

9c2c9c442287/public url

Microsoft Certified Microsoft Azure Solutions Architect Expert

LE ANH VINH

Has successfully completed the requirements to be recognized as a Microsoft Certified: Azure Solutions Architect Expert.

Date of achievement: April 10, 2021 Valid until: April 10, 2023







Certification number: H750-7150

AWS Fundamentals

https://coursera.org/share/de2e78d1dd4378206164a36df7ea9e4f



2019

MongoDB Basic

https://university.mongodb.com/course_completion/7156f0fe-5baa-404e-8c05-

94482ba3b1f9/printable







This certifies that

Le Anh Vinh

has successfully met the requirements for and was awarded a certificate in

Basics of Project Management

Issue Date:

Boher

Westers

_339087-160-180-1495

Certificate ID:

Program Director

www.ibm-institute.com/verify

SKILLS

Language	English
Tools	SVN, Git, Visual Studio 2017, Eclipse, Php Storm, VMWare/VirtualBox
Database	My SQL, SQL Server, Oracle, PostgresSQL, Redis
Programming Language	Asp.Net MVC, .Net Core, JAVA, Cake PHP, Laravel Framework, NodeJS/Express, Angular/AngularJS, ReactJs, HTML/CSS
Framework	EntityFramework, JPA, JSF, Struct, Primefaces, Ionic,
Other	OOP, Design Patern, Azure Cloud, AWS, Google Cloud Flatform

INTERESTS

I like soccer, music, travel, gym ...

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

I am always willing to learn and research to improve my Agile & Scrum skills and software techniques I have a clear career path for myself

I hope will be work in a professional environment for improving my skill and challenge with new chances

PROJECTS

OPSNOW

(09/2020 - Present)

Customer	Bespin Corporation
Description	OpsNow is a SaaS cloud management platform (CMP) for cost and resource management in multi-cloud environments. You can manage all of the public cloud in one place, and it can help you solve your various needs quickly and easily.
Team size	70
My position	Solution Architecture
My responsibilities	 Planning and tracking the project Design, Development Planning, Report Build up the server (use Azure App Service, Cloud Storage, SQL Azure) Review code Optimize code Bug Fixing Training to the new members
Technologies used	 - Azure Cloud, AWS Cloud, Google Cloud - Azure API - Java 8 - Spring Boot MVC - Lombok - Maria DB

LIFESPAN

(07/2019 - 09/2020)

Customer	IBM Corporation
Description	- This project used to manage the business in the logictics ecosystem
Team size	70
My position	Solution Architecture
My responsibilities	 Planning and tracking the project Design, Development Planning, Report Build up the server (use Azure App Service, Cloud Storage, SQL Azure) Review code Optimize code Bug Fixing Training to the new members
Technologies used	- Azure Cloud- Net core API- WPF to build application- SQL Server

Business Card

(06/2019 - 07/2019)

Customer	MTI Japan
Description	- This project used to manage the business cards, can share the card in group, company, outlook 365 ect
Team size	2
My position	Project Lead
My responsibilities	 Planning and tracking the project Design, Development Planning, Report Build up the server (use Azure App Service, Cloud Storage, SQL Azure) Review code Optimize code Bug Fixing Hold the daily meeting

Technologies used	 Google Cloud Flatform (App Engine, Vision API, Storage, Firebase) React Js, Redux, Redux Saga, Node Js, Loopback Api ect Dart, Flutter to build the android and iOS application PostgresSQL, MongoDB
-------------------	---

P & L (Profit & Loss)

(03/2019 - 06/2019)

Customer	MTI Japan
Description	- This project used to manage the costs, salary etc The project using signalR technology to live view the changes
Team size	2
My position	Project Lead
My responsibilities	 Planning and tracking the project Design, Development Planning, Report Build up the server (use Azure App Service, Cloud Storage, SQL Azure) Review code Optimize code Bug Fixing Hold the daily meeting
Technologies used	Net Core 2.0, MVC 5, Entity Framework, Azure Cloud - Jquery, Ajax, HTML/CSS - SQL Server

CARADA

(07/2017 - 02/2019)

Customer	MTI Japan
Description	- This is the web app that health care for everyone. It uses for hospitals, pharmacies, and companies. The users can register and upgrade their account to premium for managing their health every day
Team size	16
My position	Project Lead
My responsibilities	 Planning and tracking the project Development Review code Optimize code Bug Fixing Hold the daily meeting
Technologies used	Net Core 2.0, MVC 5, Entity Framework, Azure Cloud- Jquery, Ajax, HTML/CSS- Amazon SNS- SQL Server

CARD Management

(2016 - 2016)

Customer	DAC Japan
Description	- This is the web app that helps people can manage their customer's card easier
Team size	8
My position	Developer, Team Leader
	- Analysis and design - Development - Review code

My responsibilities	 Optimize code Bug Fixing Research new technology Create test cases Do interaction test
Technologies used	- Android Studio, Java - Amazon SNS - Jquery, Ajax, HTML/CSS - MySQL

Advertising System

(2017 - 2017)

Customer	DAC Japan
Description	- This is the web app that launched the advertising campaign
Team size	10
My position	Developer, Team Leader
My responsibilities	- Development - Review code - Optimize code - Bug Fixing - Research new technology - Create test cases - Do interaction test
Technologies used	- Android Studio, Java, JPA, Hibernate, Primefaces - Amazon SNS - Jquery, Ajax, HTML/CSS - MySQL

ItsOn Project

(2014 - 2016)

Customer	ItsOn USA Company
Description	- This is the web app that allow user register mobile plan for their child, users can know who has called and sent messages to their children and otherwise
Team size	10
My position	Java Developer
My responsibilities	- API Development - Review code - Optimize code - Bug Fixing - Research new technology
Technologies used	- Java, JPA, Hibernate, Primefaces - MySQL - Postman

HR Management System

(2013 - 2014)

Customer	Hitachi Japan
Description	- This is the web app that manage employees, report, salary
Team size	100
My position	Java Developer, Technical Leader
	- Analysis and design - Development

My responsibilities	- Review code - Optimize code - Bug Fixing - Research new technology - Create basic design
Technologies used	- Java, Jsf, Hibernate - Ajax, HTML/CSS - Oracle database